To Please put your hands
together for Mohit Roy. Prize
Arni Chaudhuri stands third
general deficiency subject
The fourth prize goes to Nikita
Nikita has already seen the
prize scoring the highest in
science. Next to come on stage
is Chaudhuri Legon the winner
of the fifth prize.
The sixth prize goes to Aishik
Banerjee A loud round of
applause please.
Please welcome Arkanshu Sakha,
winner of the self right gender
deficiency.
The eighth prize for general
efficiency goes to school goes
down to C the subject rise for
Hindi. Shaha Shirin Chaudhuri
also wins the eighth flight
terminal proficiency. Excuse
me. Excuse me. Sorry. Has come
ninth in class six. Earlier she
received the subject twice for
science. Joining Ujan Shri is
Pooja Moss. He too has secured
the ninth position in class
six. Earlier Ranksi is subject
wise through mathematics. Next
to come on stage is Upadhriti
Hindash who has secured the
tenth position. Congratulations
students.